const percentageFractionQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Value of 50%?",
        answer: "1/2"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 33.33%?",
        answer: "1/3"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 25%?",
        answer: "1/4"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 20%?",
        answer: "1/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 16.66% or 16 2/3%?",
        answer: "1/6"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 14.28%?",
        answer: "1/7"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 12.5%?",
        answer: "1/8"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 11.11% or 11 1/9%?",
        answer: "1/9"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 8.33%?",
        answer: "1/12"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 7.69%?",
        answer: "1/13"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 7.14%?",
        answer: "1/14"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 6.66%?",
        answer: "1/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 6.25%?",
        answer: "1/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 5.88%?",
        answer: "1/17"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 5.55%?",
        answer: "1/18"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 5.26%?",
        answer: "1/19"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 5%?",
        answer: "1/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 4.166%?",
        answer: "1/24"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 4%?",
        answer: "1/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 3.33%?",
        answer: "1/30"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 2.5%?",
        answer: "1/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 2%?",
        answer: "1/50"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 28.56%?",
        answer: "2/7"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 60%?",
        answer: "3/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 75%?",
        answer: "3/4"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 150%?",
        answer: "3/2"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 250%?",
        answer: "5/2"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 350%?",
        answer: "7/2"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 450%?",
        answer: "9/2"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 66.66%?",
        answer: "2/3"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 125%?",
        answer: "5/4"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 175%?",
        answer: "7/4"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 225%?",
        answer: "9/4"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 120%?",
        answer: "6/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 140%?",
        answer: "7/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 160%?",
        answer: "8/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 180%?",
        answer: "9/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 220%?",
        answer: "11/5"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 83.33%?",
        answer: "5/6"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 42.84%?",
        answer: "3/7"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 71.42%?",
        answer: "5/7"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 57.13%?",
        answer: "4/7"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 85.72%?",
        answer: "6/7"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 37.5%?",
        answer: "3/8"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 62.5%?",
        answer: "5/8"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 87.5%?",
        answer: "7/8"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 22.22%?",
        answer: "2/9"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 44.44%?",
        answer: "4/9"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 55.55%?",
        answer: "5/9"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 77.77%?",
        answer: "7/9"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 88.88%?",
        answer: "8/9"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 9.09%?",
        answer: "1/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 18.18%?",
        answer: "2/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 27.27%?",
        answer: "3/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 36.36%?",
        answer: "4/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 45.45%?",
        answer: "5/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 54.54%?",
        answer: "6/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 63.63%?",
        answer: "7/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 72.72%?",
        answer: "8/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 81.81%?",
        answer: "9/11"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 41.66% or 41 2/3%?",
        answer: "5/12"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 58.33% or 58 1/3%?",
        answer: "7/12"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 91.66% or 91 2/3%?",
        answer: "11/12"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 7.69%?",
        answer: "1/13"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 15.38%?",
        answer: "2/13"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 7.14% or 7 1/7%?",
        answer: "1/14"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 21.42%?",
        answer: "3/14"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 35.71%?",
        answer: "5/17"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 6.66%?",
        answer: "1/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 13.33%?",
        answer: "2/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 26.66%?",
        answer: "4/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 46.66%?",
        answer: "7/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 53.33%?",
        answer: "8/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 93.33%?",
        answer: "14/15"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 6.25%?",
        answer: "1/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 18.75%?",
        answer: "3/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 31.25%?",
        answer: "5/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 43.75%?",
        answer: "7/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 56.25%?",
        answer: "9/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 93.75%?",
        answer: "15/16"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 15%?",
        answer: "3/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 35%?",
        answer: "7/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 45%?",
        answer: "9/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 55%?",
        answer: "11/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 65%?",
        answer: "13/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 85%?",
        answer: "17/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 95%?",
        answer: "19/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 105%?",
        answer: "21/20"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 8%?",
        answer: "2/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 12%?",
        answer: "3/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 16%?",
        answer: "4/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 24%?",
        answer: "6/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 28%?",
        answer: "7/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 32%?",
        answer: "8/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 36%?",
        answer: "9/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 44%?",
        answer: "11/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 48%?",
        answer: "12/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 52%?",
        answer: "13/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 56%?",
        answer: "14/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 64%?",
        answer: "16/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 68%?",
        answer: "17/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 72%?",
        answer: "18/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 76%?",
        answer: "19/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 88%?",
        answer: "22/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 84%?",
        answer: "21/25"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 7.5%?",
        answer: "3/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 17.5%?",
        answer: "7/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 22.5%?",
        answer: "9/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 27.5%?",
        answer: "11/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 32.5%?",
        answer: "13/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 42.5%?",
        answer: "17/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 47.5%?",
        answer: "19/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 52.5%?",
        answer: "21/40"
    },
    {
        question: "Value of 57.5%?",
        answer: "23/40"
    }







];
